<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<meta
  xmlns="http://exist-db.org/xquery/repo">
  <description>Search Fringe Tracking Targets</description>
  <author>Guillaume Mella</author>
  <author>Jean-Baptiste Le Bouquin</author>
  <author>Laurent Bourgès</author>
  <author>Anthony Berdeu</author>
  <author>Jean-Philippe Berger</author>
  <website>https://searchftt.jmmc.fr</website>
  <status>stable</status><!-- stable/beta/alpha -->
  <license>AGPL-3.0</license>
  <copyright>true</copyright>
  <type>application</type>
  <target>searchftt</target>
  <prepare>pre-install.xql</prepare>
  <finish>post-install.xql</finish>
  <changelog xmlns="">
     <change version="1.5.14">
      <ul>
        <li>Move bulk form as default. Old one is <a href="onebyone.html">still online for some next releases</a>.</li>
        <li>Bulk mode recovers AO or FT targets even if sources do not respond to both constraints.</li>
        <li>Define FT and AO constraints for bulk mode.</li>
        <li>Display ranks and scores computed for every possible SCI,AO,FT combinations with two filter fields to keep the best solutions.</li>
        <li>Export main results table to csv or Aspro2.</li>
        <li>Use semicolon to enter multiple identifiers (was comma) and support to upload the list using a one column file.</li>
        <li>Refactor bulk mode code to support big catalog queries in two steps (position followed by magnitudes constraints).Timeouts still occurs on GAIA for more than ~500 identifiers. Please contact use to get a batch recipe!</li>
        <li>Resolve names and coordinates in batch mode for huge speedup on long target lists.</li>
        <li>Format decimal values (3 digits) in result tables. Use <a href="https://bottosson.github.io/posts/oklab/">oklab color space</a> with <a href="https://culorijs.org/">culori library</a> to color scores and distances values.</li>
        <li>Add a max_declinaison limit, default to 40° for VLTI case. User can override the value with max_declinaison parameter e.g: <a href="index.html?max_dist_as=40&amp;max_magK_UT=12&amp;max_magK_AT=11&amp;max_magV=16&amp;max_magR=13.5&amp;max_declinaison=90">full sky query</a></li>
        <li>Enable output table functions:<ul><li>search</li><li>add export to clipboard or CSV buttons</li><li>column selection</li></ul></li>
      </ul>
    </change>
     <change version="1.4">
      <ul>
        <!-- <li>Tests to provide a bulk form if you get many objects to query</li>-->
        <li>Refactor code : handle simbad as a catalog and prepare a later bulk form.</li>
        <li>Fix typo and Guilaume's franglish.</li>
      </ul>
    </change>
     <change version="1.3">
      <ul>
        <li>User can override default configuration limits using next parameter list:
          <ul>
            <li>max_dist_as</li>
            <li>max_magK_UT</li>
            <li>max_magK_AT</li>
            <li>max_magV</li>
            <li>max_magR</li>
            <li>eg. <a href="index.html?max_dist_as=40&amp;max_magK_UT=12&amp;max_magK_AT=11&amp;max_magV=16&amp;max_magR=13.5">try with your parameters...</a></li>
            <li>( the maximum number of targets returned may also be changed using max_rec )</li>
          </ul>
        </li>
      </ul>
    </change>
    <change version="1.2">
      <ul>
        <li>Add new catalogs as new main ones (old are hidden by default):
          <ul>
            <li><a href="https://vizier.cds.unistra.fr/viz-bin/VizieR?-source=I/353">The Guide Star Catalog, Version 2.4.2 (GSC2.4.2) (STScI, 2020)</a></li>
            <li><a href="https://gea.esac.esa.int/archive/">GAIA DR3</a></li>
          </ul>
        </li>
        <li>Fix catalog's epochs and build more accurate queries.</li>
        <li>Simbad search do not hide anymore the science star in the result table when compatible with mag filters.</li>
        <li>Enable table sortering by any column.</li>
        <li>Technical - refactor a generic code using a json config for default constraints and various catalogs.</li>
      </ul>
    </change>
    <change version="1.1.2">
      <ul>
        <li>Handle targets selection by coordinates when name resolution is not possible.</li>
        <li>Add <i class="bi bi-github"/> github repo link to the about page.</li>
      </ul>
    </change>
     <change version="1.1.1">
      <ul>
        <li>Add JMMC favicon.</li>
      </ul>
    </change>
     <change version="1.1.0">
      <ul>
        <li>Add AladinLite centered on the Science Star with fov of 3 * max-dist using 2MASS/H image server (used by guiding cam).</li>
      </ul>
    </change>
    <change version="1.0.5">
      <ul>
        <li>Add Kmag limit for AT cases in addition to previous Rmag (the tool now has two internal max_magK_UT and max_magK_AT parameters).</li>
      </ul>
    </change>
    <change version="1.0.4">
      <ul>
        <li>Main change in the layout.</li>
        <li>Add the version number in the navbar.</li>
        <li>Add the about page with release notes.</li>
      </ul>
    </change>
    <change version="1.0.3">
      <ul>
        <li><b>Add GAIA DR2 query querying ESA's archive.</b></li>
      </ul>
    </change>
    <change version="1.0.2">
      <ul>
        <li>Add missing bootstrap-icon font.</li>
      </ul>
    </change>
    <change version="1.0.0">
      <ul>
        <li>First public release.</li>
      </ul>
    </change>
  </changelog>
</meta>
